Register of the Christopher Temple Emmet Papers 1913-1974
Hoover Institution Archives
- SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1936-1973
  - The Vanishing Swastika, 1961, (with Norbert Muhlen)
  - "An Interim Plan for the Defense of Laos," January 2, 1961
  - Speech, Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy meeting, New York, January 10, 1961
  - Speech, James Monroe High School, March 14, 1961
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, March 23, 1961
  - "The Laos Crisis," March 24, 1961
  - "Memorandum on the Reasons for the Differences between France and the United States in Laos," April 1961
  - "The Present State of German-American Relations, or German-American Relations in the Shadow of the Eichmann Trial," May 1961
  - "A Judgment on the Cuban Fiasco," May 6, 1961
  - "A Comment on German Nationalism," May 9, 1961
  - "Comment on the Kennedy-Khrushcev Conference," May 22, 1961
  - "USA-Deutschland: Vertrauensbasis unerschuettert" (U.S.- Germany: Basis of Trust Unshaken), June 1961
  - "Entente Cordiale of Our Time: France and Germany," July 4, 1961
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, September 5, 1961
  - "Memorandum on Possible Areas for Negotiation between the Soviets and the West on Berlin," September 25, 1961
  - "Why the Press and the Experts Went Wrong on Kennedy's Berlin Policy: A Study of the Pitfalls of Open Diplomacy in the Age of Mass Media," November 30, 1961
  - "Comment on the Article in the July 1961 Foreign Affairs, 'Peaceful Engagement in Eastern Europe,' by Zbigniew Brzezinski and William E. Griffith," December 1961
  - "Memorandum Analyzing Kennedy's Policy in the Congo," December 14, 1961
  - "Emergency Appeal to All Freedom-Loving People: Aid Refugees from Communism in China," 1962, (with others)
  - Peace through the Soviets? preface, 1962
  - "Memorandum on the Hungarian Question," 1962
  - "U.S. Policy toward the Famine in Red China," 1962
  - "Why a Wide Response to the Attached Senatorial Questionnaire Circulated by the American Friends of the Captive Nations and by Americans of Central Eastern European Descent Would Serve the Interests of the Democratic Party as Well as the Nation as a Whole," 1962
  - "Threat to Unity on Berlin," February 17, 1962
  - Letter to the editor, America, April 7, 1962
  - "Manifesto for Captive Nations Week, 1962," June 15, 1962, (with others)
  - "Draft for Joint Statement by Members of Executive Committee of the American Friends of Vietnam, To Be Signed as Individuals, To Protect Our Tax Deductibility," July 1962
  - Speech, Captive Nations Week dinner, Assembly of Captive European Nations, Washington, July 18, 1962
  - Speech nominating Jacob Javits for Senator, Liberal Party convention, New York, September 19, 1962
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, September 27, 1962
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, October 3, 1962
  - "Memorandum on President Kennedy's Policy since Receiving Khrushchev's Letter of Virtual Surrender on the Soviet Missile Bases in Cuba," November 2, 1962
  - Speech to group of expellee leaders, Bonn, November 26, 1962
  - "Urgent Memo on Hungary and the U.N.," December 5, 1962 (Box 116)
  - "Outline of Detailed Agenda for Proposed Informal Off-the-Record Discussion or Debate on East-West Trade," 1963
  - "The U.S. Plan for a NATO Nuclear Deterrent," 1963
  - "Repercussions of the Dollar Deficit on U.S. Cold War Policy," February 20, 1963
  - "The Common Market Crisis," March 9, 1963
  - Letter to the editor, America, March 25, 1963
  - "Notes on Key Figures in Kennedy Administration as Their Records and Influence Have Evolved during the Last Two Years," April 11, 1963
  - "The Sino-Soviet Dispute," May 1, 1963
  - "In Defense of Charity," June 1963
  - "The U.S. Reversal on Hungary," June 1963
  - "Manifesto for Captive Nations Week, 1963," June 26, 1963, (with others)
  - Speech, Captive Nations Week dinner, Washington, July 17, 1963
  - "Pitfalls in a Non-Aggression Pact," August 1963
  - "Answer to a Friend's Criticism of Christopher Emmet's Orbis Article for a NATO Nuclear Deterrent," September 18, 1963
  - "Letter to a German Friend," October 1, 1963
  - "Bericht ueber meinen Besuch in Deutschland vom 12-30 Oktober 1963" (Report on My Visit to Germany of October 12-30, 1963), October 28, 1963
  - "Letter to a German Friend on Reports of a Planned American Troop Withdrawal," November 1, 1963
  - "Excerpts from a Report to German Friends on Trends of U.S. Opinion on Withdrawal of Troops from Germany," November 4, 1963
  - Speech, Assembly of Captive Nations dinner in Honor of Ole Bjorn Kraft, New York, November 13, 1963
  - "Impressions of Present European Attitudes toward de Gaulle, the U.S., and the U.S.S.R.," November 21, 1963
  - Letter to the editor, various newspapers, November 27, 1963, (with Aleksander Kutt)
  - Manifesto for Captive Nations Week, 1964," 1964, (with others)
  - Poland 1964: A Study in Lost Hopes, introduction, 1964
  - "Summary of Report for the Foreign Policy Research Institute," 1964
  - "Vorschlaege, wie man moegliche deutsch-amerikanische Missverstaendnisse waehrend des amerikanischen Wahlkampfes vermindern kann" (Proposals on How Possible German-American Misunderstandings during the American Election Campaign Can Be Reduced), 1964
  - "What Germany and the U.S. Should Do in the Present Crisis over MLF," 1964
  - "Memorandum on de Gaulle's Lifetime Record on the Communist Question in Connection with His Recognition of Red China," February 10, 1964
  - "Memorandum on the 'Relax Tensions' Fallacy," February 21, 1964
  - "Memorandum on Henry Kissinger's Three Lectures," March 23, 1964
  - "Highlights of U.S. Political Trends in February and March," March 24, 1964
  - "General de Gaulle's Foreign Policy Record," March 25, 1964
  - Testimony before U.S. House Un-American Activities Committee, May 1964 (Box 117)
  - Verpasst der Westen seine Chancen?" (Has the West Missed Its Chance?) June 1964
  - "False Priorities in American Foreign Policy," June 5, 1964
  - "Statement Presented to the Republican Platform Committee on Behalf of the American Friends of the Captive Nations," July 9, 1964
  - "Captive Nations Week," speech, July 14, 1964
  - "The Race Riots and the U.S. Elections," July 22, 1964
  - "Causes and Components of the White Backlash and Goldwater Revolution," August 5, 1964
  - "Memorandum on U.S. Policy toward Germany Submitted to Secretary Rusk and the German Desk of the State Department," August 13, 1964
  - "Which Is Stronger, Nationalism or Anti-Communism, in Eastern Europe," August 13, 1964
  - "Statement Presented to the Democratic Platform Committee on Behalf of the American Friends of the Captive Nations," August 19, 1964
  - Speech, meeting of Polish army veterans, Philadelphia, August 30, 1964
  - Speech, 4th American-German Conference, Berlin, November 1964
  - "Trends in German Relations with the United States and France," November 5, 1964
  - "The Role of the Communications Media on Influencing Public Opinion and Government Policy," November 10, 1964
  - Letter to the editor, Ukrainian Bulletin, November 15, 1964
  - "Report on the Situation in Germany," November 24, 1964
  - "Comment on Article by Alfons Dalma in the Bayern Kurier of November 27, 1965," 1965
  - "The U.S. Nuclear Monopoly and the MLF," January 14, 1965
  - "The New Crisis in Vietnam," February 11, 1965
  - "Paradox of de Gaulle and the German 'Gaullists,'" February 25, 1965
  - "Letter to a Senator Who Calls for Negotiations Now on South Vietnam," March 8, 1965
  - "President Johnson's Speech on Vietnam," April 8, 1965
  - "The Problem of Combatting Communist 'Wars of Liberation,'" April 12, 1965
  - "What's Wrong with Our Foreign Policy?" speech, New Era Club of the Educational Alliance, New York, April 23, 1965
  - "Draft of a Freedom House Statement for the Consideration of the Board, April 29th," April 26, 1965
  - "Captive Nations Week Manifesto, 1965," June 21, 1965, (with Vasil Germenji and Monsignor John Balkunas)
  - Speech, June 29, 1965
  - Speech, commemoration ceremonies for Nicola Petkov, September 18, 1965
  - Speech, St. Joseph's College for Women, Brooklyn, October 28, 1965
  - Speech, November 11, 1965
  - "Report on Henry Kissinger," December 18, 1965
  - "Philosophical Notes," December 28, 1965
  - "Captive Nations Week Manifesto, 1966," 1966, (with Vaclovas Sidzikauskas)
  - "The Causes and Cure of NATO's Erosion," January 11, 1966
  - "NATO and the American-German Alliance," January 12, 1966
  - "Memorandum to My German Friends," January 20, 1966
  - "How Peace May Come to Vietnam," February 4, 1966
  - "Anti-Communist Leaders in the Senate," February 25, 1966
  - "The Presidents's Staff," March 1, 1966
  - "Anatomy of a Communist Takeover: A Timely Theme for Congressional Hearings," March 5, 1966
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, March 6, 1966
  - "Vietnam: 'Agonizing Reappraisal,'" March 12, 1966
  - "Memorandum on the Role of the Communications Media on Influencing Public Opinion and Government Policy," April 9, 1966
  - Speech, City College of New York, April 15, 1966
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, April 17, 1966
  - "Why the U.S. Is in Vietnam," April 22, 1966 (Box 118)
  - Speech, May 17, 1966
  - "American Friends of the Captive Nations and the Struggle for Freedom," May 26, 1966
  - "Current American Criticism of Germany and Europe," May 31, 1966
  - The Lithuanian National Revolt of 1941, introduction, May 31, 1966
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, September 19, 1966
  - "Notes on German and European Reunification," October 21, 1966
  - Speech, commemorative meeting on the tenth anniversary of the Hungarian Revolution, Assembly of Captive European Nations, New York, October 24, 1966
  - "Statement on President Johnson's Speech on Eastern Europe," October 24, 1966
  - "Report on the NATO Troop Crisis," November 1966
  - Speech, Conference of Americans of Central-East European Descent dinner in honor of Senator Thomas J. Dodd, December 3, 1966
  - "The Meaning of the German Elections," December 30, 1966
  - "Comment on Article in Corriere della Sera by Ugo Stille," 1967
  - "Comment on the Article, 'The Risk Russia Is Running,' in the Economist of October 7, 1967," 1967
  - "The Real Soviet Power Play in the Near East," 1967(?)
  - Speech, Brooklyn, January 25, 1967
  - "American Public Opinion and German Nationalism," February 12, 1967
  - "American Friends of the Captive Nations Memorandum on the Premises and Methods of the Bridges-to-the-East Policy," February 20, 1967
  - Letter to the editor, America, March 17, 1967
  - Speech, Loyola University, Los Angeles, April 24, 1967
  - "Captive Nations Week Manifesto, 1967," May 9, 1967, (with Stefan Korbonski)
  - "John Foster Dulles Tenth Anniversary Project," May 18, 1967
  - "Did Moscow Lose the Mideast War?" June 27, 1967
  - "Statement on Captive Nations Week," July 12, 1967
  - "Detente: Myth or Reality?" July 25, 1967
  - "Russia's Role in Vietnam," July 29, 1967
  - "Communications Media," speech, Fairfield University, Fairfield, Connecticut, August 7, 1967
  - "Fiftieth Anniversary of a Universal Tragedy," speech, Assembly of Captive European Nations plenary meeting, New York, November 4, 1967
  - "Memorandum on the Present Situation in the Near East," November 16, 1967
  - Speech to St. George Society, Washington Irving High School, November 26, 1967
  - "Captive Nations Week Manifesto, 1968," 1968, (with George M. Dimitrov)
  - "Excerpt from a Letter to a Member of the German Bundestag on U.S.-German Differences," February 5, 1968
  - "Key Problems Affecting U.S.-German Relations and Cooperation within NATO," February 6, 1968
  - "Current Criticisms of the U.S. in Germany," February 7, 1968
  - "Some Answers to Criticism of U.S. Policy Listed in the Attached Paper," February 7, 1968
  - "Notes on the Sharpening Cold War," February 19, 1968
  - "Report on My Recent Trip to Germany," March 20, 1968
  - "German and European Attitudes toward the Non-Proliferation Treaty," March 21, 1968
  - "Reflections on the Assassination of Dr. King," April 19, 1968
  - "The Confrontation of the Two Americas," June 14, 1968 (Box 119)
  - Speech, Baltic Nations Commemoration, Assembly of Captive European Nations, New York, June 26, 1968
  - Untitled, July 6, 1968
  - "The Link between Vietnam, Berlin and the Near East," July 16, 1968
  - "The Media and the Assassinations," July 30, 1968
  - Testimony before the Democratic Platform Committee, Chicago, August 23, 1968
  - "Statement on the Czechoslovak Invasion," August 27, 1968
  - "The U.S. Elections," October 23, 1968
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times, November 13, 1968
  - "Captive Nations Week Manifesto, 1969," 1969, (with Jozef Lettrich)
  - "Joint Statement: American Friends of the Captive Nations, Conference of Americans of Central and Eastern European Descent," February 6, 1969, (with Monsignor John Balkunas)
  - "Report on Objections in Germany to Signing the Non-Proliferation Treaty Now," February 19, 1969
  - Speech, International Peasant Union, March 1, 1969
  - "Report on United States Senate Action on the Non-Proliferation Treaty," March 28, 1969
  - "Post-War Germany," speech, University of Pennsylvania Foreign Policy Research Institute, Philadelphia, July 1969
  - "The ABM Debate," July 2, 1969
  - Letter to the editor, New York Times Magazine, July 25, 1969
  - Speech, 16th Plenary Session, Assembly of Captive European Nations, September 16, 1969
  - "Memorandum on Talk by Sam Brown at Council on Foreign Relations," December 4, 1969
  - "Captive Nations Week Manifesto, 1970," 1970, (with Alfreds Berzins)
  - Untitled, February 26, 1970
  - "Missing Element in the Debate," June 30, 1970
  - "Implications of the Bonn-Moscow Pact," August 25, 1970
  - Speech, Assembly of Captive European Nations, September 15, 1970
  - "Reflections of an 'Unreconstructed' New Deal Liberal of the New Leader School," October 28, 1970
  - "Captive Nations Week Manifesto, 1971," 1971, (with Vasil Germenji)
  - "Memorandum on Policy toward Eastern Europe," June 30, 1971
  - Speech, Assembly of Captive European Nations plenary session, September 21, 1971
  - Speech on the 15th anniversary of the Hungarian Revolution, Philadelphia, October 24, 1971
  - Speech, Baltic Women's Council, New York, March 5, 1972
  - "Report on Trip to Germany," March 14, 1972
  - Speech, June 19, 1972
  - "East-West Trade," speech, Assembly of Captive European Nations, New York, September 19, 1972
  - "The Captive Nations in 1972," October 2, 1972
  - "Analysis of the U.S. Elections," October 13, 1972
  - "Germany as Seen from the United States on the Eve of the Two National Elections," November 6, 1972
  - "Captive Nations Week Manifesto, 1973," 1973, (with Stefan Korbonski)
  - "Summary of David Martin's Activities on Behalf of the Iron Curtain Refugees and the Captive Nations," 1973
  - "Letter to a European Friend on the 'New Nixon,'" January 11, 1973
  - "Report on Trip to Germany, February 22nd-March 7th, 1973," March 10, 1973
  - "Reflections on Watergate," May 25, 1973
  - "More Reflections on Watergate," July 27, 1973
  - "A Memorial to Nicola Petkov," speech, September 22, 1973
  - "Memorandum on the Work of David Martin," October 17, 1973
  - "Memorandum Proposing a Testimonial Dinner in Honor of David Martin," October 26, 1973
  - "Letter to a German Friend (Member of the CDU Party)," December 10, 1973
- RADIO BROADCAST TRANSCRIPTS, 1939-1973
  Notes for and typewritten transcripts of radio broadcasts, arranged chronologically.
  - "Can America Keep Out of War?" WEVD, New York, 1939 (Box 120)
  - Untitled, WMCA, March 16, 1939
  - Untitled, Poughkeepsie, New York, April 15, 1939
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 16, 1939
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 30, 1939
  - Untitled, 194?
  - "Is Disarmament Possible?" 194?
  - Untitled, New York University Forum, WEVD, New York, December 26, 1940
  - News commentary, WEVD, New York, March 14, 1941
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, March 21, 1941
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, March 28, 1941
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, April 4, 1941
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, April 11, 1941
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, April 18, 1941
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, April 25, 1941
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 2, 1941
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 9, 1941
  - "Should We Agitate for a Second Front?" WEVD, New York, October 6, 1942
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, June 17, 1943
  - Untitled, Round Table Forum, WEVD, New York, June 29, 1943
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, July 2, 1943
  - Untitled, Round Table Forum, WEVD, New York, July 13, 1943
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, July 16, 1943
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, July 23, 1943
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, July 30, 1943
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, August 6, 1943
  - "Who Are the American Fascists? Round Table Forum, WEVD, New York, August 10, 1943
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, August 13, 1943
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, August 20, 1943
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, August 24, 1943
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, August 28, 1943
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, September 3, 1943
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, September 7, 1943
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, September 10, 1943
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, September 17, 1943
  - "Small Powers and the Moscow-Cairo Agreement," WEVD, New York, December 14, 1943
  - "Future of France," Round Table Forum, WEVD, New York, January 10, 1944
  - "What Did Pravda Mean?" Round Table Forum, WEVD, New York, January 25, 1944
  - Untitled, Round Table Forum, WEVD, New York, February 8, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, March 17, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, March 31, 1944
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 2, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, May 26, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, June 23, 1944
  - "The First Victim of Japanese Aggression," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 27, 1944
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, June 30, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, July 7, 1944
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, July 11, 1944
  - Bastille Day Program, WNYC, July 14, 1944
  - "The Democratic Convention," WEVD, New York, July 19, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, August 11, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, August 18, 1944
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, August 24, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, September 1, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, September 8, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, September 29, 1944
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 3, 1944
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 17, 1944
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 19, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, October 20, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, October 27, 1944
  - "The Catholic Bishops' Peace Principles," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 28, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, November 3, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, November 10, 1944
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, November 14, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, November 17, 1944
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, November 24, 1944
  - Untitled, November 27, 1944
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, November 28, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, December 1, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom Forum, WEVD, New York, December 6, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, December 8, 1944
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, December 12, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, December 15, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, December 22, 1944
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, December 29, 1944
  - Untitled, 1945(?) (Box 121)
  - Untitled, Freedom Forum, WEVD, New York, 1945
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, January 5, 1945
  - Untitled, Freedom Forum, WEVD, New York, January 10, 1945
  - "Two Lessons from Our Temporary Set-back in France," Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, January 12, 1945
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, January 19, 1945
  - "Should We Break Diplomatic Relations with Spain Now? Newspaper Guild Forum on Spain, WMCA, January 23, 1945
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, January 26, 1945
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, February 2, 1945
  - Untitled, Freedom Forum, WEVD, New York, February 7, 1945
  - Untitled, February 9, 1945
  - "Will the Wallace Plan Work?" Freedom Forum, WEVD, New York, February 14, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, February 16, 1945
  - "Argentina and Economic Sanctions," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, February 20, 1945
  - Untitled, Freedom House Program, WEVD, New York, February 23, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, March 2, 1945
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 6, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, March 9, 1945
  - "Communism in the U.S.," WEVD, New York, March 16, 1945
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, March 20, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, March 23, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, March 30, 1945
  - "The Military Picture in China," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 3, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, April 13, 1945
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, April 17, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, April 20, 1945
  - "Truman and Unity," Freedom Forum, WEVD, New York, April 25, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, April 27, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 4, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 11, 1945
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 15, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 18, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, May 25, 1945
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, May 29, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, June 1, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, June 8, 1945
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 12, 1945
  - Untitled, June 22, 1945
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, June 26, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, July 20, 1945
  - "Lessons of the British Elections," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, July 24, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, July 27, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, August 10, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, August 17, 1945
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, August 21, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, August 24, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, August 31, 1945
  - "German War Criminals," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, September 4, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, September 14, 1945
  - "Negotiations with Britain," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, September 18, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, September 21, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, September 28, 1945
  - "Australia and the Big Five," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 2, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, October 5, 1945
  - "New Zealand," Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 16, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, October 19, 1945
  - "An Answer to Russell Davenport," WMCA, October 23, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, October 26, 1945
  - Untitled, Foreign Affairs Round Table, WEVD, New York, October 30, 1945
  - Untitled, WEVD, New York, November 2, 1945